[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "Why do you think you've been able to inspire that kind of loyalty?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "think", "you", "'ve", "been", "able", "to", "inspire", "that", "kind", "of", "loyalty", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "I am the wrong person to ask.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "the", "wrong", "person", "to", "ask", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "What do you work on other than making great music, but in terms of your relationship with an audience, what do you work on you think that brings you that extra time?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "work", "on", "other", "than", "making", "great", "music", ",", "but", "in", "terms", "of", "your", "relationship", "with", "an", "audience", ",", "what", "do", "you", "work", "on", "you", "think", "that", "brings", "you", "that", "extra", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "The truth.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "truth", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "As someone who'd always been in the background like you say, the moment you went center stage, did you in that moment realize, wow, OK, this is what it's all about?", "question_tokens": ["As", "someone", "who", "'d", "always", "been", "in", "the", "background", "like", "you", "say", ",", "the", "moment", "you", "went", "center", "stage", ",", "did", "you", "in", "that", "moment", "realize", ",", "wow", ",", "OK", ",", "this", "is", "what", "it", "'s", "all", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "WP", "-NONE-", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "No, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["OK"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 85, "question": "Did you that night?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "that", "night", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 86, "answer": "Yes, yes, I did.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", ",", "I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "But when you got that reaction from the crowd, and that was the first time you'd had it, what was the experience like to you?", "question_tokens": ["But", "when", "you", "got", "that", "reaction", "from", "the", "crowd", ",", "and", "that", "was", "the", "first", "time", "you", "'d", "had", "it", ",", "what", "was", "the", "experience", "like", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "It was like floating.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "like", "floating", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 116, "question": "What's the answer in your case?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "answer", "in", "your", "case", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 117, "answer": "Well, for me, I kind of knock me over.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "for", "me", ",", "I", "kind", "of", "knock", "me", "over", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "Wouldn't you think that fame would be the greatest thing to happen to a person, you know?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "n't", "you", "think", "that", "fame", "would", "be", "the", "greatest", "thing", "to", "happen", "to", "a", "person", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "Well, I think that everyone who's not famous assumes it is the greatest thing that could happen.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "everyone", "who", "'s", "not", "famous", "assumes", "it", "is", "the", "greatest", "thing", "that", "could", "happen", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "``", "NNP", ",", "''", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 143, "question": "-- whoa, how's she handle this, you know?", "question_tokens": ["--", "whoa", ",", "how", "'s", "she", "handle", "this", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "And yet the fact that you mentor the acts on \"Idol,\" you've done it a couple of times --", "answer_tokens": ["And", "yet", "the", "fact", "that", "you", "mentor", "the", "acts", "on", "``", "Idol", ",", "''", "you", "'ve", "done", "it", "a", "couple", "of", "times", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 148, "question": "If you're concerned about what may happen?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "'re", "concerned", "about", "what", "may", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 149, "answer": "I would do that every day if I could.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "do", "that", "every", "day", "if", "I", "could", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "Or is it just a pain in the backside?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "is", "it", "just", "a", "pain", "in", "the", "backside", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "I don't think of myself as being famous.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "of", "myself", "as", "being", "famous", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "Have you met anybody in the last 20 years who didn't know who you were?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "met", "anybody", "in", "the", "last", "20", "years", "who", "did", "n't", "know", "who", "you", "were", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "Well, yes, sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "yes", ",", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last 20 years"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "RB", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "But not often?", "question_tokens": ["But", "not", "often", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "But not often, no.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "not", "often", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "JJR", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 194, "question": "How much of it has she brought on herself?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "of", "it", "has", "she", "brought", "on", "herself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 195, "answer": "I just remember them just driving her crazy.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "remember", "them", "just", "driving", "her", "crazy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 208, "question": "Does it worry you that we're going to see more of that with people who just may be off psychologically, a little flawed anyway?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "worry", "you", "that", "we", "'re", "going", "to", "see", "more", "of", "that", "with", "people", "who", "just", "may", "be", "off", "psychologically", ",", "a", "little", "flawed", "anyway", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "RP", "RB", ",", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 209, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 212, "question": "It's a drug, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "drug", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "It's a drug.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "drug", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "That's what happens, right?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "what", "happens", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "Well, on that bombshell, we are going to take a quick break so the audience can recover.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "on", "that", "bombshell", ",", "we", "are", "going", "to", "take", "a", "quick", "break", "so", "the", "audience", "can", "recover", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 239, "question": "What advice would you give that Barry Manilow?", "question_tokens": ["What", "advice", "would", "you", "give", "that", "Barry", "Manilow", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "It's -- just stick to your guns.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "--", "just", "stick", "to", "your", "guns", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barry Manilow"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "Who's they?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "'s", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "Everybody but the audiences.", "answer_tokens": ["Everybody", "but", "the", "audiences", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "ORGAN: What was that like for you?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "What", "was", "that", "like", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "Well, it was dreadful.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "was", "dreadful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 267, "question": "Did I say something about our noses?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "I", "say", "something", "about", "our", "noses", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 268, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "You know the concord hooter arrives, you know?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "the", "concord", "hooter", "arrives", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 297, "question": "Are you a vain man, would you say?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "a", "vain", "man", ",", "would", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 298, "answer": "I'm as vain as the next guy.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "as", "vain", "as", "the", "next", "guy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "Probably more so now, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Probably", "more", "so", "now", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJR", "IN", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "But only with you or with people like you who remind me I'm not the average guy.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "only", "with", "you", "or", "with", "people", "like", "you", "who", "remind", "me", "I", "'m", "not", "the", "average", "guy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Vegas"]}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 311, "question": "I say hello to the people out there and that's it, you know?", "question_tokens": ["I", "say", "hello", "to", "the", "people", "out", "there", "and", "that", "'s", "it", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 312, "answer": "The average guy isn't earning stratospheric sums of money being a huge headline act in Vegas.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "average", "guy", "is", "n't", "earning", "stratospheric", "sums", "of", "money", "being", "a", "huge", "headline", "act", "in", "Vegas", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", ":", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "Where did it go?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "did", "it", "go", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "I had hired a -- my first business manager.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "had", "hired", "a", "--", "my", "first", "business", "manager", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "Since that experience, did you get wiser about money?", "question_tokens": ["Since", "that", "experience", ",", "did", "you", "get", "wiser", "about", "money", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "I did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "Do I know how much I'm worth?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "I", "know", "how", "much", "I", "'m", "worth", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "That's sad though, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "sad", "though", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "You know, I thought so.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "thought", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "You remember that one?", "question_tokens": ["You", "remember", "that", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 371, "question": "I mean, I think that it would work again today, don't you?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "I", "think", "that", "it", "would", "work", "again", "today", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 372, "answer": "So do I.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "do", "I", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "How would you feel ideologically, if McDonald's came to you now and said, would you front a commercial for us?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "feel", "ideologically", ",", "if", "McDonald", "'s", "came", "to", "you", "now", "and", "said", ",", "would", "you", "front", "a", "commercial", "for", "us", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", ",", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "CC", "VBD", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "Oh, I would love it.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "would", "love", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["McDonald"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "But the reason I -- the reason I was dwelling on the sad songs and the heartbreak was that you're quite private bloke, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["But", "the", "reason", "I", "--", "the", "reason", "I", "was", "dwelling", "on", "the", "sad", "songs", "and", "the", "heartbreak", "was", "that", "you", "'re", "quite", "private", "bloke", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "PRP", ":", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "I am.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "Had your heart broken?", "question_tokens": ["Had", "your", "heart", "broken", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "Never.", "answer_tokens": ["Never", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "Never?", "question_tokens": ["Never", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "Never.", "answer_tokens": ["Never", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 409, "question": "Seriously?", "question_tokens": ["Seriously", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 410, "answer": "Yes, never.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "never", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "You've never ever been in love or had your heartbroken?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "never", "ever", "been", "in", "love", "or", "had", "your", "heartbroken", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "PRP$", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "I've been in love, but I -- I'm lucky enough never to have my heart broken.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "been", "in", "love", ",", "but", "I", "--", "I", "'m", "lucky", "enough", "never", "to", "have", "my", "heart", "broken", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "How have you avoided what's struck everybody else?", "question_tokens": ["How", "have", "you", "avoided", "what", "'s", "struck", "everybody", "else", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "WP", "POS", "NN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "Shoot, Piers, I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["Shoot", ",", "Piers", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "CC", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 436, "question": "What's the definition of romance?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "definition", "of", "romance", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 437, "answer": "I guess, it's whatever -- I think romance, and love for that sake, is whatever anybody wants it to be.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "guess", ",", "it", "'s", "whatever", "--", "I", "think", "romance", ",", "and", "love", "for", "that", "sake", ",", "is", "whatever", "anybody", "wants", "it", "to", "be", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "For anybody in the fame game, is it sensible to open your book up like that, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["For", "anybody", "in", "the", "fame", "game", ",", "is", "it", "sensible", "to", "open", "your", "book", "up", "like", "that", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "TO", "JJ", "PRP$", "NN", "RP", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "For them, it might be wonderful for them.", "answer_tokens": ["For", "them", ",", "it", "might", "be", "wonderful", "for", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ":", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "Am I?", "question_tokens": ["Am", "I", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "Yes, but the old mystique from celebrity -- the star game used to be everyone was on a plinth and you didn't really know much about them.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "but", "the", "old", "mystique", "from", "celebrity", "--", "the", "star", "game", "used", "to", "be", "everyone", "was", "on", "a", "plinth", "and", "you", "did", "n't", "really", "know", "much", "about", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "How do you come up with them?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "come", "up", "with", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "The best ones that I've come up with are not at the piano, when I'm walking around.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "best", "ones", "that", "I", "'ve", "come", "up", "with", "are", "not", "at", "the", "piano", ",", "when", "I", "'m", "walking", "around", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "``", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 555, "question": "When you do something like \"Mandy,\" where did that come to you?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "do", "something", "like", "``", "Mandy", ",", "''", "where", "did", "that", "come", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "``", "NNP", ",", "''", "WRB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "You know I didn't write \"Mandy.\"", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "I", "did", "n't", "write", "``", "Mandy", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mandy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "''", "VBD", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 560, "question": "\"If I Should Love Again,\" how did you come up with that?", "question_tokens": ["``", "If", "I", "Should", "Love", "Again", ",", "''", "how", "did", "you", "come", "up", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["``", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", ",", "''", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 561, "answer": "\"If I Should Love Again\" was a --", "answer_tokens": ["``", "If", "I", "Should", "Love", "Again", "''", "was", "a", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 602, "question": "Was she one of the greatest showman you have played with?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "she", "one", "of", "the", "greatest", "showman", "you", "have", "played", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 603, "answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Annie Lennox"]}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 630, "question": "She says is there anyone you have met that really made you feel star struck?", "question_tokens": ["She", "says", "is", "there", "anyone", "you", "have", "met", "that", "really", "made", "you", "feel", "star", "struck", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 631, "answer": "ANILOW: Yeah, Annie Lennox.", "answer_tokens": ["ANILOW", ":", "Yeah", ",", "Annie", "Lennox", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 649, "question": "Isn't that amazing?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "that", "amazing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 650, "answer": "It is amazing.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "amazing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 669, "question": "Quite interesting, what would you be doing if you hadn't gone into music, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Quite", "interesting", ",", "what", "would", "you", "be", "doing", "if", "you", "had", "n't", "gone", "into", "music", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 670, "answer": "I can't imagine myself not --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "ca", "n't", "imagine", "myself", "not", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBG", "IN", "WRB", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 671, "question": "Do you ever wonder?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "ever", "wonder", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 672, "answer": "I would have been playing in some bar at night, complaining about how nobody understands me.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "have", "been", "playing", "in", "some", "bar", "at", "night", ",", "complaining", "about", "how", "nobody", "understands", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "CD", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 699, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 700, "answer": "I've never heard of that one, I must say.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "never", "heard", "of", "that", "one", ",", "I", "must", "say", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "IN", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 703, "question": "That there was one of my songs?", "question_tokens": ["That", "there", "was", "one", "of", "my", "songs", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "EX", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 704, "answer": "\"Let's Hang on.\"", "answer_tokens": ["``", "Let", "'s", "Hang", "on", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 729, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 730, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "CD", "VBD", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 742, "question": "When you say wrote in a dream, do you actually mean these things come to you sometimes in dreams?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "say", "wrote", "in", "a", "dream", ",", "do", "you", "actually", "mean", "these", "things", "come", "to", "you", "sometimes", "in", "dreams", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 743, "answer": "Well, this one did, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "this", "one", "did", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 746, "question": "Do you wake up?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "wake", "up", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 747, "answer": "This one woke me up.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "one", "woke", "me", "up", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 761, "question": "Do you jump out of bed and write it all down?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "jump", "out", "of", "bed", "and", "write", "it", "all", "down", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "IN", "VBN", "CC", "JJ", "PRP", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 762, "answer": "I did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 774, "question": "Who of the modern crop catches your eye?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "of", "the", "modern", "crop", "catches", "your", "eye", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 775, "answer": "The modern crop.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "modern", "crop", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 776, "question": "Any other?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "other", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 777, "answer": "Well, I like Sting's work.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "like", "Sting", "'s", "work", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 784, "question": "Do you really think I'm going to tell you that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "really", "think", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "tell", "you", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 785, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 789, "question": "What is the song that you literally can't hear anymore?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "song", "that", "you", "literally", "ca", "n't", "hear", "anymore", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 790, "answer": "I would never answer that question!", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "never", "answer", "that", "question", "!"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]